Guide to the Joshua A. Fishman Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1 Correspondence to and from J. A. Fishman and J.A. Fishman/G. S. Fishman, 1926-1992
  - 1979 August (Cont'd. ) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 1979 July (Cont'd. ) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 1979 July (Cont'd. ) (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 1979 June (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 1979 June (Cont'd. ) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 1979 May (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - 1979 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 1979 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 1979 May (Cont'd. 3) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 1979 April (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 1979 March (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 1979 March (Cont'd.) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 1979 February (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 1979 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 1979 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 1979 January (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 1979 January (Cont'd.) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - 1980 General (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - 1980 Undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 1980 December (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 1980 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - 1980 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 1980 November (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 1980 November (Cont'd.) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 1980 October (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 1980 October (Cont'd.) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 1980 September (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - 1980 September (Cont'd.) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 1980 August (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 1980 July (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 1980 July (Cont'd.) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 1980 June (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 1980 June (Cont'd.) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 1980 May (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 1980 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 1980 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - 1980 April (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 1980 March (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - 1980 March (Cont'd.) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 1980 February (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 1980 February (Cont'd.) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 1980 January (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 1980 January (Cont'd.) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - 1981 General (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 1981 December (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 1981 December (Cont'd.) (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - 1981 November (Cont'd.) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - 1981 October (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - 1981 October (Cont'd.) (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - 1981 September (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - 1981 September (Cont'd.) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - 1981 August (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - 1981 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - 1981 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - 1981 July (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - 1981 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - 1981 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - 1981 July (Cont'd. 3) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - 1981 June (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - 1981 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - 1981 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - 1981 May (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - 1981 May (Cont'd,) (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - 1981 April (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - 1981 April (Cont'd.) (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - 1981 March (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 1981 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - 1981 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - 1981 February (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - 1981 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - 1981 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 1981 January (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 1981 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - 1981 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 1982 General (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 1982 Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 1982 December (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - 1982 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - 1982 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 1982 November (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 1982 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 1982 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 1982 October (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 1982 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - 1982 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - 1982 September (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 1982 September (Cont'd.) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 1982 August (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - 1982 August (Cont'd.) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - 1982 July (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - 1982 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - 1982 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - 1982 June (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 1982 June (Cont'd.) (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - 1982 May (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 1982 May (Cont'd.) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 1982 April (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 1982 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - 1982 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - 1982 March (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 1982 March (Cont'd.) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - 1982 February (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - 1982 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 1982 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 1982 January (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - 1982 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - 1982 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - 1982 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1983 General (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - 1983 General (Cont'd.) (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - 1983 Undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - 1983 December (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 1983 December (Cont'd.) (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - 1983 November (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - 1983 November (Cont'd.) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - 1983 October (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - 1983 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 1983 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 1983 September (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - 1983 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 1983 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 1983 August (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 1983 August (Cont'd.) (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - 1983 July (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 1983 July (Cont'd.) (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 1983 June (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - 1983 June (Cont'd.) (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - 1983 May (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 1983 May (Cont'd.) (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 1983 April (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 1983 April (Cont'd.) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 1983 March (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 1983 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 1983 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 1983 February (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 1983 February (Cont'd.) (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 1983 January (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - 1983 January (Cont'd.) (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - 1984 General (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - 1984 Undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 1984 December (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 4) (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 5) (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - 1984 December (Cont'd. 6) (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - 1984 November (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - 1984 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - 1984 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 1984 November (Cont'd. 3) (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 1984 November (Cont'd. 4) (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 1984 October (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - 1984 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - 1984 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - 1984 October (Cont'd. 3) (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 1984 September (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 1984 September (Cont'd.) (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - 1984 August (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - 1984 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - 1984 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - 1984 July (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - 1984 July (Cont'd.) (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - 1984 June (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - 1984 May (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 1984 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 1984 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - 1984 April (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - 1984 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 1984 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 1984 March (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 1984 March (Cont'd.) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 1984 February (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 1984 February (Cont'd.) (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 1984 January (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 1984 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 1984 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - 1984 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - 1985 General (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 1985 Undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 1985 December (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - 1985 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - 1985 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - 1985 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - 1985 November (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 1985 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 1985 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 1985 November (Cont'd. 3) (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 1985 October (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 1985 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 1985 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - 1985 October (Cont'd. 3) (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 1985 October (Cont'd. 4) (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 1985 September (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 1985 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - 1985 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 1985 September (Cont'd. 3) (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 1985 August (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 1985 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - 1985 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - 1985 July (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 1985 July (Cont'd.) (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 1985 June (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 1985 June (Cont'd.) (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 1985 May (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 1985 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - 1985 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 1985 May (Cont'd. 3) (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 1985 April (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 1985 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 1985 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 1985 April (Cont'd. 3) (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 1985 March (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - 1985 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 1985 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - 1985 March (Cont'd. 3) (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 1985 March (Cont'd. 4) (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - 1985 February (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 1985 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 1985 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 1985 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 1985 February (Cont'd. 4) (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - 1985 January (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - 1985 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 1985 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 1985 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 1986 General (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 1986 December (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 1986 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 1986 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 1986 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 1986 December (Cont'd. 4) (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 1986 December (Cont'd. 5) (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 1986 November (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 1986 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 1986 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - 1986 November (Cont'd. 3) (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 1986 November (Cont'd. 4) (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - 1986 October (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - 1986 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - 1986 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - 1986 October (Cont'd. 3) (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - 1986 October (Cont'd. 4) (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 1986 September (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 1986 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 1986 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - 1986 September (Cont'd. 3) (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - 1986 August (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - 1986 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - 1986 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - 1986 July (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - 1986 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - 1986 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - 1986 July (Cont'd. 3) (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - 1986 June (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - 1986 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - 1986 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - 1986 May (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - 1986 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - 1986 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - 1986 May (Cont'd. 3) (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - 1986 April (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - 1986 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - 1986 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - 1986 March (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - 1986 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - 1986 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - 1986 March (Cont'd. 3) (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - 1986 February (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - 1986 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - 1986 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - 1986 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - 1986 January (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - 1986 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - 1986 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - 1986 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - 1987 General (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - 1987 Undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - 1987 December (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - 1987 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - 1987 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - 1987 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - 1987 December (Cont'd. 4) (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - 1987 December (Cont'd. 5) (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 1987 November (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 1987 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - 1987 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - 1987 October (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - 1987 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - 1987 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - 1987 September (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 1987 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - 1987 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - 1987 August (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - 1987 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - 1987 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - 1987 July (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - 1987 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - 1987 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - 1987 June (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - 1987 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - 1987 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - 1987 May (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - 1987 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - 1987 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - 1987 May (Cont'd. 3) (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - 1987 April (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - 1987 April (Cont'd.) (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - 1987 March (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - 1987 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - 1987 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - 1987 March (Cont'd. 3) (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - 1987 February (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - 1987 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - 1987 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - 1987 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - 1987 January (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - 1987 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - 1987 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - 1987 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - 1988 General (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - 1988 Undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - 1988 December (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - 1988 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - 1988 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - 1988 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 1988 December (Cont'd. 4) (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - 1988 November (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - 1988 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - 1988 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 1988 October (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - 1988 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 1988 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - 1988 September (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - 1988 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - 1988 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - 1988 September (Cont'd. 3) (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - 1988 September (Cont'd. 4) (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - 1988 August (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - 1988 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - 1988 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - 1988 July (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - 1988 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - 1988 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 1988 June (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - 1988 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - 1988 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - 1988 May (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - 1988 May (Cont'd.) (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - 1988 April (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - 1988 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - 1988 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - 1988 April (Cont'd. 3) (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - 1988 March (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - 1988 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - 1988 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - 1988 February (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - 1988 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - 1988 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 1988 January (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 1988 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - 1988 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - 1988 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - 1989 General (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - 1989 Undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - 1989 December (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - 1989 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - 1989 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - 1989 November (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - 1989 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 1989 October (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 1989 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - 1989 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - 1989 September (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - 1989 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - 1989 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - 1989 September (Cont'd. 3) (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - 1989 August (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - 1989 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - 1989 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - 1989 August (Cont'd. 3) (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - 1989 July (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - 1989 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 1989 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - 1989 June (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - 1989 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - 1989 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - 1989 May (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - 1989 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - 1989 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - 1989 April (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - 1989 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - 1989 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - 1989 April (Cont'd. 3) (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - 1989 March (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - 1989 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - 1989 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - 1989 February (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - 1989 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - 1989 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 1989 January (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 1989 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 1989 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - 1989 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - 1990 General (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - 1990 General (Cont'd. 1) (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - 1990 General (Cont'd. 2) (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Jewish New Year Cards (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - 1990 December (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - 1990 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - 1990 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - 1990 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - 1990 December (Cont'd. 4) (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - 1990 December (Cont'd. 5) (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - 1990 November (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - 1990 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - 1990 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - 1990 October (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - 1990 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - 1990 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - 1990 October (Cont'd. 3) (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Fira Bramson - Vilna (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - 1990 September (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - 1990 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - 1990 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - 1990 September (Cont'd. 3) (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - 1990 August (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - 1990 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - 1990 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 1990 July (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - 1990 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - 1990 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - 1990 June (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - 1990 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - 1990 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - 1990 June (Cont'd. 3) (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - 1990 May (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - 1990 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - 1990 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - 1990 April (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - 1990 April (Cont'd.) (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - 1990 March (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - 1990 March (Cont'd.) (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - 1990 February (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - 1990 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - 1990 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - 1990 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - 1990 January (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - 1990 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - 1990 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - 1990 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - 1991 General (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - 1991 General (Cont'd.) (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - 1991 Jewish New Year Cards (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - 1991 December (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - 1991 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - 1991 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - 1991 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - 1991 November (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - 1991 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - 1991 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - 1991 November (Cont'd. 3) (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - 1991 October (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - 1991 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - 1991 October (Cont'd. 2) (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - 1991 October (Cont'd. 3) (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - 1991 September (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - 1991 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - 1991 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - 1991 August (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - 1991 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - 1991 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - 1991 July (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - 1991 June (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - 1991 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - 1991 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - 1991 May (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - 1991 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - 1991 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - 1991 May (Cont'd. 3) (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - 1991 April (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - 1991 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - 1991 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - 1991 February-March, E-Mail from Israel during the Scud Missile attacks - Gulf War (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - 1991 February-March (Cont'd. 1), E-Mail from Israel during the Scud Missile attacks - Gulf War (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - 1991 February-March (Cont'd. 2), E-Mail from Israel during the Scud Missile attacks - Gulf War (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - 1991 March (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - 1991 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - 1991 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - 1991 March (Cont'd. 3) (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - 1991 February (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - 1991 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - 1991 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - 1991 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - 1991 January (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - 1991 January (Cont'd. 1) (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - 1991 January (Cont'd. 2) (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - 1991 January (Cont'd. 3) (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - 1991 January (Cont'd. 4) (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - 1991 January (Cont'd. 5) (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - 1992 General (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - 1992 General (Cont'd.) (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - 1992 December (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - 1992 December (Cont'd. 1) (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - 1992 December (Cont'd. 2) (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - 1992 December (Cont'd. 3) (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - 1992 November (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - 1992 November (Cont'd. 1) (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - 1992 November (Cont'd. 2) (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - 1992 October (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - 1992 October (Cont'd. 1) (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - 1992 September (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - 1992 September (Cont'd. 1) (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - 1992 September (Cont'd. 2) (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - 1992 August (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - 1992 August (Cont'd. 1) (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - 1992 August (Cont'd. 2) (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - 1992 July (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - 1992 July (Cont'd. 1) (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - 1992 July (Cont'd. 2) (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - 1992 June (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - 1992 June (Cont'd. 1) (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - 1992 June (Cont'd. 2) (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - 1992 May (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - 1992 May (Cont'd. 1) (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - 1992 May (Cont'd. 2) (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - 1992 April (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - 1992 April (Cont'd. 1) (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - 1992 April (Cont'd. 2) (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - 1992 March (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - 1992 March (Cont'd. 1) (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - 1992 March (Cont'd. 2) (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - 1992 February (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - 1992 February (Cont'd. 1) (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - 1992 February (Cont'd. 2) (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - 1992 February (Cont'd. 3) (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - 1992 January (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - 1992 January (Cont'd.) (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - An alphabetic card-file index: name of person to and from, date, language, his/her institution/ organization, (1935-1992), A-Br (Box 117)